<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="aboutApp">

        We have developed this application to help people in which there are all emergency numbers of India. You can dial these
        numbers anytime and anywhere. It has been given a lot of activities so that you can see your <b>History</b> and your
        <b>Recent Activities</b>. If you wish, you can save these numbers in your phone and share these numbers with others by
        <b>Emergency Number</b> activity. What is the work of every activity for your help, it is written below. "\n\n\n"


        <b>Features</b> "\n\n"
        <b>SOS: </b> With the help of this button your can add any number on <b>QuickTouch</b> one by on, so that you can
        dial any number
        very quickly.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Feedback: </b> If you would like or have some suggestion about app so you can send the feedback by click on three
        dot which showing on home screen at top right.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>QuickTouch: </b> Here are all the number that you add to the help of SOS so that you can dial numbers very quickly.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Recent: </b> Here are all your recent activities.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Emergency Numbers: </b> Here are all Indian Emergency numbers and here you can <b>SHARE</b> and <b>SEND</b>
        these numbers these number, <b>Just Swipe Right</b> the list item.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Saved: </b> Here are all number that you saved in your phone in emergency number activity.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>History: </b> Here are all your call history which you can <b>DELETE</b> just swipe right.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Setting: </b> Where you can delete your data.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        This application is developed by developer: <b>AKASH SAINI</b>. For the purpose of help people in any kind of emergency.
        "\n"
        "\n"
        <b>Developer: </b> Akash Saini

    </string>

</resources>